Minahil Akhtar

Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan



minahilakhtar2235@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/minahil-akhtar

Summary

I am a MERN Stack and WordPress Developer with experience in modern technologies such as React.JS, Redux, Node.JS, Express.js, REST APIs, MongoDB, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap. I am passionate about what I'm doing and see every task as a challenge and an opportunity to get better.

My portfolio site minahilakhtar.github.io/cv

My Personal Website https://minahilakhtar.com

Experience



p Frontend Web Developer

Upwork

Jan 2021 - Present (2 years 5 months)

Frontend Developer

Bulls Orbit

Mar 2022 - Apr 2023 (1 year 2 months)

I have worked at Bulls Orbit as a Front end developer There I Completed a lot of tasks related to web development.

Frontend Web Developer

Frontend Mentor

Mar 2021 - Jan 2022 (11 months)

https://www.frontendmentor.io/profile/minahilakhtar

Education



ĕ Zero To Mastery Academy

Feb 2020 - Mar 2021



Asean Online Education AOE



Army Public School - (APSACS)

(A) freeCodeCamp

Licenses & Certifications

Digital Marketing - DigiSkills.pk 6727RGTPQ

Facebook Ads - Asean Online Education AOE 192816199672

CSS & JavaScript - Certification Course - Udemy UC-724f3a84-6e24-4713-9e0f-14228640c28e

Google Ads Search Certification
49530046

- Digital Marketing Master Class FEMPROW
- **The Fundamental Of Digital Maketing** Google Digital Garage WTP FPL EEV
- JavaScript Essential Training LinkedIn AVsUkDaaMFz2jlx0L_tjEQ2ayl7l
- HTML Essential Training LinkedIn
 Addl3VLWTGsp1hdEL6R35_6m2Avr
- CSS Essential Training LinkedIn
 AY26hCblGorlqYc30aeNwOaiuwLE

Skills

HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Bootstrap • Tailwind CSS • React.js • MongoDB • Node.js • REST APIs • WordPress